[{"answer": "How many great white sharks --", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 6, "question": "How many gun murders were there in Britain?", "qSentId": 5}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, as somebody who favors more gun control, I really hope that Alex Jones does more TV, because, you know, look, you've been quite articulate in making the case for gun control.", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "What was your overall reaction to that extraordinary exchange with Alex Jones last night?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "Let me -- he made one substantial -- they've made two substantial arguments.", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "-- that he raised about the actual argument?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Well, to me it was really a fairly typical performance for Alex Jones.", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "What did you make of what Alex Jones' performance was like and what does it tell you about that kind of gun rights on the rather extreme side of the gun rights lobby?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "I fear that it is not going to be very successful.", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "Is it going to be successful?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "And harder to get, the more extreme variety of weapon, for those who may be disturbed.", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "So why can't we begin to have the same kind of public health approach, not to ban guns, but to make them a little bit safer in American homes?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Initially, I was infuriated and disturbed by his reaction.", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "What was your reaction to that as somebody who lost a loved one in the Aurora massacre?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "I'm cautiously optimistic.", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "Do you believe that there is now momentum to get real action or not?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "The car is not specifically mentioned in the Bill of Rights.", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "What's the difference?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "First off, we don't own M-4s or M-16s.", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "Why would you want to give one of these killing machines to one of your children, anyway?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "No, that's not what I said.", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "So your answer is that everybody in a movie theater would be armed with an AR-15?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "All right.", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Where does that lead America to other than utter Wild West hell?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "No, I think America is a country that revels in violence, that was born in violence, that loves the image of the frontiersman and the cowboy and having guns.", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "Do you believe that Sandy Hook represents any kind of tipping point in favor of new gun legislation?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Well, I think, Piers, that it begins with a discussion in the court of public opinion.", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "How do we try to move forward to a point of some consensus, where the gun lobby are persuaded that these AR-15 type, military-type machine guns, what they really are, are actually not part of this debate in any sane way?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "I do want to point out, based on the conversation last night, that it's not even worth mentioning this guy's name.", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Do you hold out any hope that if it does go to Congress, they'll pass anything involving gun control legislation?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "But Buzz Bissinger, this is all well and good.", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Because they just want to be re-elected at the end of the day, right?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "Well, I feel that they are afraid.", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "What do you make of that?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "No one needs any of that stuff.", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Why does anyone need multiple rounds?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Thank you for asking, Piers.", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "First of all, how is your client?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "Well, that's the case.", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Does she really know what happened to her?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "ITZSIMMONS: Well, there were already other witnesses that testified at the preliminary.", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "If not, are there witnesses you think who will be able to?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "Quite simply.", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "How do you defend him?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "He is 16 years old.", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "Does your client accept that he behaved badly on the night, just generally?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "Look, I'm not here to do what social media is doing, OK.", "docId": "130108pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "Do you believe that there is sufficient doubt about your client's involvement in the sexual aspect of this case, that he will be acquitted?", "qSentId": 606}]